Guide to the Myers Family Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Family Correspondence, 1916-1985; Series II; 4.25; (11 boxes)
  - Correspondence, 1934 (Box 13, Folder 200-02)
  - Correspondence, 1935 (Box 13, Folder 203-05)
  - Correspondence, 1936 (Box 13, Folder 206)
  - Correspondence, 1937 (Box 14, Folder 207-11)
  - Correspondence, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 212-16)
  - Correspondence, 1939 Jan-Aug (Box 14, Folder 217-21)
  - Correspondence, 1939 Sep-Dec (Box 15, Folder 222-23)
  - Correspondence, 1940 (Box 15, Folder 224-25)
  - Correspondence, 1941 (Box 15, Folder 226)
  - Correspondence, 1942 Feb-Sep (Box 15, Folder 227-33)
  - Correspondence, 1942 Oct-Dec (Box 16, Folder 234-36)
  - Correspondence, 1943 (Box 16, Folder 237-44)
  - Correspondence, 1944 Feb-May (Box 16, Folder 245)
  - Correspondence, 1944 Jul-Dec (Box 17, Folder 246-51)
  - Correspondence, 1945 (Box 17, Folder 252-58)
  - Correspondence, 1946 (Box 17, Folder 259-64)
  - Correspondence, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 265-68)
  - Correspondence, 1948 (Box 17, Folder 269)
  - Correspondence, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 270)
  - Correspondence, 1950 (Box 18, Folder 271)
  - Correspondence, 1951 (Box 18, Folder 272-73)
  - Correspondence, 1952 (Box 18, Folder 274)
  - Correspondence, 1953 (Box 18, Folder 275-77)
  - Correspondence, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 278)
  - Correspondence, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 279)
  - Correspondence, 1956 (Box 18, Folder 280)
  - Correspondence, 1957 (Box 18, Folder 281)
  - Correspondence, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 282)
  - Correspondence, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 283)
  - Correspondence, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 284)
  - Correspondence, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 285)
  - Correspondence, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 286)
  - Correspondence, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 287)
  - Correspondence, 1967-69 (Box 18, Folder 288)
  - Correspondence, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 289)
  - Correspondence, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 290)
  - Correspondence, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 291)
  - Correspondence, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 292)
  - Correspondence, 1975-80 (Box 19, Folder 293)
  - Correspondence, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 294)
  - Correspondence, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 295)
  - Correspondence (Box 19, Folder 296-98)
- Family Papers, 1908-1982; Series III; 3.75; (9 boxes)
  Series III, Family Papers, is divided into three alphabetically arranged sections, Richard E. Myers Papers, Alice Lee Herrick Myers Papers, and Richard Herrick Myers Papers.
  - RICHARD E. MYERS PAPERS
    - Biographical information, 1929-46, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 299)
    - Death
      - Letters of Sympathy, A-L, 1958 (Box 20, Folder 300-16)
      - Letters of Sympathy, M-Z, 1958 (Box 21, Folder 317-26)
      - Obituaries, 1958 (Box 21, Folder 327)
      - Prayers, 1958 (Box 21, Folder 328)
      - Sympathy cards, 1958 (Box 21, Folder 329)
    - Diary, 1918-19 (Box 21, Folder 330)
    - Legion of Honor, 1949 (Box 21, Folder 331)
    - Music societies, 1942, 1950, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 332)
    - Scrapbooks: indexes (Box 21, Folder 333)
      See also: Boxes 29-30, folders 456-58
    - Sheet music, 1931-77, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 334-35)
      See also: Box 30, folder 459
    - Theater, 1946-47, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 336)
    - Writings
      - Articles, 1948, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 337)
      - Invitation to the Château by J. Anovich, translated by R. E. Myers, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 338)
      - Poetry, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 339)
  - ALICE LEE HERRICK MYERS PAPERS
    - Address books, [1958, 1975?], n.d. (Box 22, Folder 340)
    - American and European society, 1942-57, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 341)
    - Biographical information, 1910-75, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 342)
    - Christmas lists, 1933-66, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 343-44)
    - Datebooks, 1969-82 (Box 22, Folder 345-50)
    - Diaries, 1918, [1973?], n.d. (Box 22, Folder 351)
    - European vacations
      - Itinerary and photographs, 1928, 1938 (Box 23, Folder 352)
      - Memorabilia, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 353)
    - Fashion, 1948-49, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 354)
    - Food, 1946, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 355)
    - Paris: lease and receipts, 1930-49 (Box 23, Folder 356)
    - Passports, 1960-72 (Box 23, Folder 357)
    - Red Cross, World War I
      - Correspondence, 1918 (Box 23, Folder 358-60)
      - Correspondence, 1919, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 361-63)
      - Clippings, 1918-19, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 364-65)
      - Identifications, 1918 (Box 23, Folder 366)
      - Memorabilia, 1919, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 367-68)
      - Orders and papers, 1918-19 (Box 23, Folder 369)
      - Photographs, 1918-19, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 370-71)
    - Scrapbooks
      See: Box 31, folders 460-61
    - World War II
      - Clippings, 1938-46, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 372-73)
      - Correspondence, 1942 (Box 24, Folder 374)
      - Correspondence, 1944 (Box 24, Folder 375-78)
      - Correspondence, 1945 (Box 24, Folder 379-80)
      - Correspondence, 1946 (Box 24, Folder 381)
      - Papers, 1939, 1942, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 382)
    - Writings
      Articles
      - Chicago Daily News, 1932 (Box 24, Folder 383)
      - Ladies Home Journal, 1932 (Box 24, Folder 384)
      - English compositions, 1908 (Box 24, Folder 385-86)
      - English compositions, 1910 (Box 24, Folder 387-88)
      - English compositions, 1912 (Box 24, Folder 389-90)
      - Poetry, 1945, 1962 (Box 24, Folder 391)
    - Writings of others
      - "The Library Window" by Annie, 1915 (Box 24, Folder 392)
      - Hitchcock
      - "My Most Unforgettable Character" by, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 393)
      - Hope Livermore Wheelwright
  - RICHARD HERRICK MYERS PAPERS
    - Avon Old Farms
      - Diploma, 1940 (Box 25, Folder 394)
      - Papers, 1937-40, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 395)
      - Yearbook, 1940 (Box 25, Folder 396)
    - Biographical information, 1925-43, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 397)
    - Death
      - Letters of sympathy, A-G, 1943-44, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 398-406)
      - Letters of sympathy, H-Z, 1943-44, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 407-23)
      - Letters of sympathy, unidentified, 1943-44, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 424-26)
      - Memorials, 1945, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 427)
      - Obituaries, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 428)
      - Sympathy cards, 1943-44, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 429)
    - Royal Air Force, World War II
      - Address book, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 430)
      - Correspondence, 1941-42 (Box 27, Folder 431-35)
      - Correspondence, 1943 Jan-Jul (Box 27, Folder 436-40)
      - Correspondence, 1943 Aug-Dec (Box 28, Folder 441-44)
      - Correspondence (Box 28, Folder 445)
      - Datebooks, 1942, 1943 (Box 28, Folder 446)
      - Diary, 1942 (Box 28, Folder 447)
      - Memberships, 1942, 1943 (Box 28, Folder 448)
      - Memorabilia, 1942, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 449)
      - Notes, 1943, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 450)
      - Papers, 1942, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 451)
      - Photographs, 1942-43, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 452-54)
- Oversize, 1933-1971; 2.75; (3 boxes)
  The papers in Oversize are arranged in Series order.
  - PERSONAL CORRESPONDENCE
    - Burden, William, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 455)
  - FAMILY PAPERS
    - Richard E. Myers Papers
      - Scrapbooks, 1933-57, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 456-57)
      - Scrapbook, 1944-49 (Box 30, Folder 458)
      - Sheet music, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 459)
    - Alice Lee Herrick Myers Papers
      - Scrapbooks, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 460-61)
- Restricted Fragile Papers, 0.5; (1 box)
  Conditions Governing Access
  Box 32: Restricted fragile material. Reference surrogates have been substituted in the main files. For further information consult the appropriate curator.
  - Box 1, folders 10, 11, 14, 16, 17 (Box 32, Folder 462)
  - Box 2, folder 25 (Box 32, Folder 463)
  - Box 3, folder 33, 38, 39 (Box 32, Folder 464)
  - Box 3, folders 46, 47 (Box 32, Folder 465)
  - Box 4, folders 54, 57, 58, 60 (Box 32, Folder 466)
  - Box 5, folders 72, 74, 76 (Box 32, Folder 467)
  - Box 5, folders 80, 84, 86 (Box 32, Folder 468)
  - Box 6, folders 87, 96, 103 (Box 32, Folder 469)
  - Box 7, folders 108-10 (Box 32, Folder 470)
  - Box 8, folders 117, 118, 126, 129 (Box 32, Folder 471)
  - Box 9, folder 142 (Box 32, Folder 472)
  - Box 10, folders 144, 147 (Box 32, Folder 473)
  - Box 11, folder 156 (Box 32, Folder 474)
  - Box 11, folders 161, 167, 168, 170 (Box 32, Folder 475)
  - Box 12, folders 173, 174 (Box 32, Folder 476)
  - Box 13, folders 186, 188 (Box 32, Folder 477)
  - Box 13, folders 199, 200 (Box 32, Folder 478)
  - Box 14, folders 207, 210, 221 (Box 32, Folder 479)
  - Box 15, folders 226, 229, 239, 243 (Box 32, Folder 480)
  - Box 17, folders 246-50 (Box 32, Folder 481)
  - Box 17, folders 252, 253, 256, 260, 263, 266, 269 (Box 32, Folder 482)
  - Box 18, folders 270, 275, 276, 282 (Box 32, Folder 483)
  - Box 19, folder 298 (Box 32, Folder 484)
  - Box 20, folders 301-04, 306, 308 (Box 32, Folder 485)
  - Box 20, folders 309, 311, 314-16 (Box 32, Folder 486)
  - Box 21, folders 318, 320, 321, 323, 325, 326, 331 (Box 32, Folder 487)
  - Box 23, folders 354, 355, 362, 365 (Box 32, Folder 488)
  - Box 23, folders 366-68 (Box 32, Folder 489)
  - Box 25, folders 397, 398, 402, 405 (Box 32, Folder 490)
  - Box 26, folders 410, 412-14, 416 (Box 32, Folder 491)
  - Box 26, folders 417, 418, 420, 424 (Box 32, Folder 492)
  - Box 26, folder 425 (Box 32, Folder 493)
  - Box 27, folder 427 (Box 32, Folder 494)
  - Box 28, folders 443, 451 (Box 32, Folder 495)